Glove breaking in beast of prey
Please run an errand for me...
Don't wanna!
Mum is busy with the chores, so you must...
Oh, come on
No is no
I don't wanna go out today!
At home you don't read
anyway,but simply kill times
So you should be asked
by shopping something
I'd rather die than going out!
Be reasonable, young man!
Giant is angry again, huh?
Don't speak that name...
IMy body trembles just by listening to his name!
You're so hopeless!
You can't just stay home
for your whole life.
Brace yourself!
But it's really terrible.
I really can take you any more
Give me back the magic weapon
Glove breaking in beast of prey
Any beast animal would speak
as soon as a little touched with it
Really?
For example...
Nobita, if you stay home
then listen to your mom...
Come... come... come...
Sit down
Get down
wonderfu, Doraemon
Lend this to me,to me
Note:It's only effective for five minutes
remember? Only five minutes.
No more fears
Come out,come out,Gian
Come out...
Wow... it's Gian
What are you doing actually?
I am still scared...
can't come close to it
Not come close nothing can work
You do have gloves with you, be brave!
I'll be brave.
Right, I have gloves with no fear.
Show your courage.
What do you think which team would win?
Of course giant
Gian...Wow...
(Giant sounds the same like Gian)
You really can talk...
No, I can't get rid
of fears to him
Really hard to do. How to make you
close to him? Well, lets' do this way
Hi,how are you doing? Touching...
I made it
Sit down
Lie prone
Wonderful, I made it
Success comes only with care
Go
Right, so is it.
In fact it's so easy.
Really marvelous.
Well, let everyone see it
Come again...
What do you say?
Nothing
Everybody will admire me.
It's real, full of
exciting breaking in beast of prey
You forget yourself immediately
What do you say?
Nothing
You wait and will see
Damned creature, you are
actually here. Nobita, wake up
Hi, Gian rushes here with anger
Everybody, don't worry.
Have a good look at
Come on...monkey
Touch... touch...
Sit down
Lie prone
How marvelous
Come on... stand upside down
Now have a look
at the more difficult show
I will have it jump onto this platform
and then pass through this circle.
If succeed,
everybody gives an applause,please.
Come... jump over.
Really good
Like a really master
Per request from the audience
I will raise the circle's height
Come... jump over
Stupid, once again
Hi, time is over.
Hello, five minutes passed
Remember for me...
Nothing, nothing. Although I just
escaped in hurry
Touching with this glove slightly
no fears to any beast of prey
Doraemon, help me
I don't' want to be beaten for you.
You come over to me, Nobita
Finished...
Ancestors, come on
Salute
Why so shy?
This is polite. This is a
heritage from my ancestors.
Suneo's ancestor was a samurai
He was very strong and
save his master various times.
Since then we are minister president
generations for generations.
Under the master your ancestor
is the highest ranked.
Every family has its own origin.
Not your turn to open big mouth.
Damned guy
So it is, he laughs at us.
Never lose to him.
Take Time machine to see your ancestor.
What are you doing? Hurry up.
I know
In such a big mountain
Because he is a hunter
Does anybody live in such remote area?
Hi, hit... it's big Tanuki
What Tanuki...
Thank goodness I am a robot
Please be careful, okay?
Sorry, my eyes are small.
Doraemon, is that him?
I don't know.
Who are you?
I am hunter Nobisaku
Its' really him.
Run away...
Help me
stay away...
Why come to us?
You should get some chickens,
rabbits or mice
Succeed, my technique is really not bad.
Really like Suneo.
Are you Suneo's ancestor?
Behave yourself
Do you think who I am'?
I am Honegawa's family first
son, Honegawa Omaru
You can be so impolite to Samurai
Knee down and make kowtow at once
I will cut off your heads
Omaru...
Father
What are you doing,
get ready to battlefield.
Well, finally march on?
Father, I will come make it.
Very reliable. The master
will be happy with your success.
Sarnorai is very handsome
I really also want to be Samorai...
Then...
What, I should go to battle?
Right, then you get power and money.
No, no, I don't want money.
Really useless
Well,Nobisaku's face
looks very like yours
You go to battlefield for him.
I will adjust that later.
No, no, I don't want money.
Do you want to lose to Suneo this way?
I understand.
Then no worries.
Now let's see where to bring the armor and the sword.
March on... march on...
Please wait a moment
Lend me your armor, please.
What nonsense are you talking
I just want to be on battlefield.
Ma' the strongest one in this village
Try it if you don't believe that.
Look at my bullet.
What a beautiful bullet, must be very
valuable.Exchange that with my armo,ok
But that's my...
I'll remove my clothes, you can have 'em!
Can we do so?
Bamboo 'copter
transparent cloak, supper gloves
Now there's no need to fear.
Whose side should I take?
Whomever you want
I want to ally the just party.
In wars, both sides think they're the ones who're just, that's just how the wars go.
Catch the head of the opposite
hand him over to one's own head.
Either of the war parties thinks their
side would be the right and justice one
Catch the head of the opposite
hand him over to one's own head.
Bye then.
Oh, so he's the warlord.
Okay, I'll be invisible.
Hand him to the opposite head.
Really, the victory belongs to our side.
I also caught one alive.
It's Omaru
Well done, behead these two.
No need to kill them.
You're going way too far.
Do you want to defy my orders?
Behead this guy too while you're at it.
Behead me? Not in your lifetime!
Take that!
Now I'll help these poor guys.
I'll be back in no time!
I'll leave the rest to you.
With these gadgets by your side, you have the upper hand.
That's right,
exchange with them immediately.
Be clear that you saved the lord and Sunemaru.
This way your ancestor
became 2nd most powerful man
I just told you our ancestor was hunter
Nothing has changed
That's odd, let's see what happened using the Time TV.
I saved you, my lord!
Well done! From today, you're going to be my right hand.
What's my ancestor doing now?
For the first time
in my life I hunted wild pig.
How hopeless.
The Girl Like a White Lily
During WWII, Japan's important cities were under constant bombardment by the Allies.
For safety, children were evacuated to the deep countryside,
along with their friends and teachers...
This was called the kids' evacuation.
Conditions were harsh and there was absolutely no way to study.
Instead we dug air-raid shelters, tilled fields, that was our daily life, then.
I would be very hungry all the time.
That chocolate tasted so good. Even today I can still reminisce its' taste.
Really romantic story.
Do you know the name
and address of that girl?
Who are you talking about?
A girl, "as pretty as a White Lily!"
Daddy!
Watch it! She'll get the wrong idea!
Be honest with me!
It was a story from my childhood!
Oh.
I'm taking this back.
Daddy must love her very much.
Surely...
He should have taken a picture or something.
I got it! We can go take one! With the time machine!
Great idea! Then we can give the photo to dad as a souveneir.
Inside this temple.
Nobody here.
Can I help you?
Everybody is working in fields.
Nobody has time for lesson
not even any food.
Even kid goes to fieldwork.
What would be Japans future?
Oh my god, oh my god.
Why are you so lazy? Nobi, do you
think this would count anything?
Sorry, teacher, my hand is
full of bubbles, stomach empty.
He is daddy
This little difficulty counts nothing.
Think of
the hard soldiers on battlefield.
Well, 30 minutes break.
NO need to beat him
Really too extreme.
Nobi, you are not allowed to
rest before finishing this field.
How pitiful, can not see that any more.
Very bad, unconscious
Sleep aside the roads like that
soon teacher will criticize you.
It does not matter
You replace him
Although you say that, I can't.
Supper gloves
All problems
will be solved if using this.
You see we almost finish it.
Great
Oh painful.
What is this kind of girl's haircut?
Really not formal.
Give you this for haircut.
I don't want it, very ugly.
Wait a minute for restoring
it to the original.
In such a chaotic time
all we Japanese have to be united.
Produce more for the country
but you have such haircut
Well Nobi, you finish that alone.
Really unimaginable.
Hm, very good, this is Japanese boy.
Thanks for your help we
have nothing to do.
Today's work ends here.
Very bad, we'll be punished
heavily. Run away.
Strange, daddy disappears
He must be on riverside
Right
Then we'll wait for white lily coming
Can you restore my haircut
during this waiting time?
30 minutes hair formula.
Almost dawn,
white lily is still not here.
Look for her in the near.
Don't' run away.
I said.
Deodorant your body. I'll get
some suitable cloths for you.
Mom, I just want to die
and finish everything.
Borrowed from the cloth shelf over there
This is girl's cloth.
3D minutes are over.
body is white, hair is very long
eyes are round, girl...
I remember in Doraemon's pocket...
Chocolate
Wait a moment
In fact it's such a story.
Films are taken, but
That's right, if symbolized with flower
just like white lily,
beautiful and clean
This memory remains
beautiful memory forever.
Say one thing but mean others.
I am care... ful going out.
Nobita
Why do you want to escape?
No... Doraemon helped me.
You look at this chaos yourself
Can you keep your own room in order?
Agreed with Shizuka to play outside.
I will get it in order when coming back
No nonsense any more.YOU won't do
anything when coming back, bad boy.
Sit down
You are already grade four
You can't even order your
room. Aren't you ashamed?
Hi... mom soon as you open
your mouth, you'll never stop
You have to bring your things in order..
Doraemon is even watching aside.
Nobita, What attitude do you have?
It's time to save him.
Well, if you think so
let's start from me.
Nobita is really marvelous.
It does not matter not listen to your
mom. Go and play with Shizuka.
What's the matter actually?
Only because of this flute.
This is called flute say one mean others
Its frequency can make people crazy.
What they actually do is
the opposite what they think.
In fact so, therefore very angry mom
paises me on the contrary
Wonderful, so I can
play without any concern.
Don't think of that too beautiful.
Doraemon, why come to that
land Shizuka have
arranged, as I said
Look, if you do so with heart
you can finish that immediately.
Doraemon, I borrowed a wrong flute.
Doraemon, what do you want to do then?
I want to take a bath
and have my body cleaned.
Stop it, Nobita...
Stop it, Stop it ...Help
It would be a waste for this
interesting flute if not used well.
Look at your cloths. They are so
beautiful however to look at
Thank you, but compared to
yours it's still very different.
What, you even dare
to ware that ugly stuff?
She wares the same anyway...
What
Suneo, this is baseball bat
I just bought. Let me try it.
No, please, help
Suneo, please hit me with this.
Shizuka, I take good stuff
and show you, Shizuka...
Damned, somebody disturbs
just when met good chance.
Hi, don't move, no sound.
Shizuka, what's the matter...
it's me, Nobita
Get him away...
How is it finally, well...
Come in, come in, please.
Hm, I am...
Come in, come in...
Sit down wherever you want.
I'll get some tea.
Hm, not so complicated.
Nobita...
What's the matter, Shizuka
How come you become like that?
That man is a thief.
Thief...
Get some tea
Well, then I have to go, see you.
Nobita, you escape on your own? Not good
Don't be shy, come back again.
Oh yes, I am a thief to steal something
You damned guy...
Run away
Stop...
You guy are good.
Oh, Sorry
This is my purse. Take it.
Then this pullover also for you.
Even this pair of trousers.
What else then'?
Oh yes, underwear also for you.
No more, no more, I don't want underwear
How are you, today's weather
is very good...see you
Don't run away.
Stop...
I say stop...
Sorry, don't' feel strange with it.
You bloody guy...
Why am I so bad?
That's right, think about it thoroughly.
What do you say, damned guy.
What's the matter?
I am thief, catch me, please.
Nobita, you made the room
so clean, really marvelous
Really?
I am really very happy
Nobita listens to me so well.
Do it, Doraemon
Nobita...
Doraemon,
don't open your big mouth any more.
Nobita, why do you listen so much to
mom. I won't forgive you today.
Forgive me, I won't listen to
her any more. Sorry...
asia_cartoons@sinarnan.cor-n
Time camera
Very strange, over there...
Daddy, I have something to ask you...
What's the matter? Why sighing?
Any concerns? Daddy
Sighing does not solve
anything. Do you feel bad?
I am calling mom coming.
Well, no need, no need to call mom here
Very strange How to do then'?
What's the matter, tell us.
Actually I lost my purse
while buying cigarettes.
Purse
Disappears
I can find
it even running back immediately.
I looked around there, but found nothing
It's too bad. If mom knows
that, she will be very upset.
And she will never stop if getting upset
Daddy, what to do? Mom is terrible.
That's right, what to do?
You are talking about whom
what very terrible?
Nothing, it has nothing with daddy.
Really about nothing?
Really strange person
Mom is gone
How to you from tomorrow
if purse not found?
No cigarette to smoke,
nothing to eat nor to play
Al joys in life will disappear.
Daddy is really pitiful.
Doraemon, help him, please
Try this
Time camera
Wow, how beautiful...
Doraemon, take me also one picture
lam ready, Doraemon
Nobita, this is not a camera
for now, but for the past.
Taking a picture 30 minutes ago
for example in this room, first set.
I am taking picture
Already done, how great
Let me have a look
Oh yes, 300 minutes ago
I was eating Dorayaki
What, I did not appear?
Besides Doraemon is very crafty
even eats on his own,unforgiveable
Sorry
Damned, you selfish guy
Because there is only one
Only one
should be divided into half each.
Hurry up,
find daddy's Purse is more important
That's right,
we have to find daddy's Purse.
Here, it's here.
Daddy bought cigarette here
Well, take a picture and see
Doraemon, it was 40 minutes ago.
40 minutes ago, well...
Take a picture and see
Taken
Perfect...
Let me see, Purse taken
We succeed
This means that his purse was
dropped on the way from hereto home
Take pictures while walking
Turn to the corner
Standing and chatting with others
Walked to here... wow...
Nothing strange until here
Stopped and watching something.
Started walking again
Continued walking
Well, it was Nobita, what is she doing?
Nobita
Wow, what a wonderful camera
Take me a picture
Hm, well... I am very busy now
Don't be stingy, hurry up with photo
Taken, Doraemon
What is this picture?
No choice, that was 40 minutes ago.
I was not taken...
Daddy disappears
Where was daddy, then?
Here... there...?
Every side has to be taken in picture.
Not here
not here
Appears
Daddy watched here the baseball game
Take another one and see
Hm, daddy even disturbed them
by playing something with them
Hm, daddy lost his
purse when running there.
Dropped
Over there
Try to find it
Very strange, it should be dropped here
but nothing
Maybe taken away by somebody
Adjust the time and
take another picture, then.
In fact it was picked up by a dog.
Come this way.
Walk along this way straight ahead
Walk further
Not yet
I know, over there
Jumped into the window.
Here
Sorry for bothering
Is it here?
Found
Nobita, Doraemon, thank you both.
This camera is great.
YOU should be encouraged.
So it was, Doraemon
can you lend the camera to me?
Okay, please.
Take a picture and then
we know who stole Dorayaki
Wait a moment, please
Proposal war
Wow, so many foods
What's the matter, mom'?
Today is the 12th anniversary of
the marriage of you daddy and me
I am back.
Enjoy your food,
today's foods are the best.
Daddy, help yourself, please.
Thank you
Tell us the memory on your wedding day
Your daddy told me...
If you don't marry me
I will kill myself.
Hi, no nonsense, okay?
Daddy, what did you say
You proposed me
and cried asking me
Daddy, you even lie
in front of kids.
I lied? You are talking nonsense.
What
It seems become very terrible.
I remember very clearly
Daddy proposed first.
It was not me, you proposed first.
It was daddy
It was you
Very difficult
Anyway, if we can make it clear
they will never stop arguing.
No other choice,
let's find out the truth.
Here we are, this is Shyowa39 year
month, day in Hibitani park
Where was Nobita's mom?
Hm, over there
Where well
That was Nobita's mom...
Totally different from today.
What
Nothing, just kidding
Can't take it, so slow...
She said there are important things
to announce, but she is late.
One hour late
It seems that daddy was late.
Ms. Tamako
Mr. Nobi
That's daddy
Sorry, Ms. Tamako
I am even one hour late.
I want to be back.
Ms. Tamako, Sorry
Ms. Tamako, wait a moment
fills. Tarnako,
I was wrong, please excuse me.
Ms. Tamako...
Finally you know wrong.
Mr. Nobi, I forgive you, go ahead.
Damned, even use this method.
Actually I wanted propose
her. Forget it. I won't.
It seems that things are wrong...
What do you mean important thing?
I don't know
Who are you
Mr. Nobi
Please, okay?
Damned guy, remember that
Take it
thanks brother
Don't; spend it casually.
Not thought of being
cheated for money by one's own sister
Oh yes, what is Ms. Tamako doing?
Forget it,
that damned woman with no feeling.
That woman...
I never want to see her again.
It seems that things went wrong.
In this way it wouldn't go to marriage
thus no Nobita born
That can go
think of something, Doraemon
What's this?
Human simulates Robot
Look at this carefully, Robot
Well, it turns
to be the same as that person.
Just the same like daddy.
Ms. Tamako...in fact you are here
Never talk to you.
Don't be angry, please marry me.
Otherwise I will kill myself right here.
Mr. Nobi, please don't be so.
I promise you now, stop it
Mr. Nobi, in fact you have really
good feeling. I am so happy.
Then I wait for you over there.
Well, then this woman
went to daddy
Mr. Nobi
Ms. Tamako, what's the matter?
You even did that kind.
Sorry, Mr. Nobi, I was wrong.
Can you please marry me?
Well...really, Ms. Tamako
Ms. Tamako...
wait for me a moment...
Good, well done,
this makes us not concerned
Mr. Nobi...
Ms. Tamako...
Let's build up a happy family.
Well, we work hard together.
Well, very successful.
But, whether they argued we don't know
Become peaceful again? Very concerned.
Both daddy and mom are not here.
What to do
Found it'?
No
Maybe divorced
both gone from home away
Not good, they can't do so...
It's not important
at all who proposed first.
Now we are the happiest
Is that not enough'?
That's right. Why become angry
for such tinny matter?
Really sorry
No, I should apologize.
These two are really good friends.
That's right.
Asia_cartoons@sinarnan.cor-n
Machine arranging things before
It seems that this movie
is very interesting
Well, ask daddy bring me see it.
Daddy, a movie is currently in
cinemas. Bring me to see.
Its' called star war.
It's a quite sensational movie.
All tickets are sold out 1 month before
Many just buy standing tickets.
Cinemas are fully crowded.
See it half a year later what
Well, Dorayaki
This must be Doraemon's
Well, eat it away
Very strange, why can eat anything?
What's the matter?
Damned
You can never eat it.
Well, is this Doraemon's?
Really nothing careless.
But it's really strange.
Of course, I wrote reservation card.
Nobody except me can eat it.
Reservation card...
This means this
Only Doraemon can eat Dorayaki.
If you want or do anything
Just write it on reservation card
put it into reservation machine
Nobody else can take
what I have reserved.
Right
Well, can I reserve that one'?
Start war
Well, you can see
that movie any time
Wonderful that's great...
Then write it onto this card and
put it into the machine.
Star war, three o'clock this
afternoon two good seats...Nobita
Is that okay?
No problem at all
What nonsense are you talking?
It's true, already reserved.
How can you reserve it?
Well, I bet with you.
If not reserved, I will do everyday
whatever daddy tells me to do.
Then you'll learn hard everyday.
Well...okay
So he promised me to bring me there.
That's fine.
But I am concerned again.
If nothing reserved well
I have to learn hard everyday.
Don't worry.
Really no problem?
Try it if still in doubt.
Hi, is Nobita in?
What?
I bring you the book you want to borrow.
Really, lam coming, wait a moment.
Thank you,
I have been expecting this book.
Wonderful, I'm so happy.
How are you?
What's the matter?
What?
It seems that it's very interesting.
Lend me for a look.
When can I see it?
After they two finish
How come?
Really angry, Doraemon
You can leave these matters to machine.
Well, I want to be
the first one reading that book.
Well, start reading.
Strange, why can't it be opened?
Really strange, why do I not want to see
it before Nobita sees it'?
Can I see it first?
That's right, see it first.
Thank you
He brought it for me to see first.
Look, I made it.
Can you use past things?
The stamp last time can not be found.
Of course you can also use it.
Really?
Then I go and buy it.
Be careful on the way.
I bought it... I bought it...
Really great, really bought it.
Those who
have not bought can not accept it
Show them what you bought.
Don't do so, boring.
Suneo, Gian, Haruo
wait at home before I go.
Finished writing.
Hi, get ready to start up
if you want to go.
Well, I am coming.
Every time so many people on
bus. So I hate going out.
Seats on bus are reserved
There must be seats.
Sorry
So many people, you can see absolutely.
I say no problem.
My name is Nobita, I want two seats.
Mr. Nobi's seat is
ready. Please come in.
You see... Daddy, go.
Thank you.
It's really different with good seat.
Very nice view, daddy
But, it's really a strange day
I am back.
Hello, Nobita
What's the matter?
The phone is ringing
all the time since evening.
Phone...
Because you asked those three people
waiting for you at home absolutely.
So they call you angrily
since evening all the time.
You never come however we wait for you
making me not going out at all.
I had appointment before...
Doraemon, you pick up the phone.
I can't take it.
Well, hi...
You guy, I will invite you
if you come to school tomorrow.
Go there
I don't dare going there.
Anyway, just go there.
Not even think of me...
But you enjoyed a lot yesterday
In fact you were bloody...
Call a doctor waiting for
you at home. No need.
asia_cartoon@hotmail.com
Tanuki machine changing the body.
You listen to me
lam quite good at sport.
Only at sport?
Yes, at others...
Really Gian?
Very hot... hot... hot...
Really too extreme
That means
Oh yes, long time ago I thought
Nobita's face looked like...
What
Now I finally know.
It's Tanuki
Really alike.
You can't say so.
You are also laughing, right'?
Damned, this guy Suneo...
Too much extreme
Yes
You even say Nobita looks like Tanuki...
You said that correctly.
Doraemon...
Sorry, Sorry...
Forgive me, Please
Nobita is abused
meaning I am abused.
I have to revenge.
Tanuki machine changing body.
Is this eyeglass or tail?
What
Listen to my explanation
There used to be Tanuki playing
humans. Do you know that?
In the mountains, although
day time, it turns to be night.
Make people lose their way change the
figures to monster, shit to food
Really change your body if put this on?
That's right, glass frame is antenna
sending your brain waves to others.
Making others fantasies about you
Hi...don't make me an experiment
Well, it's night with moon shine
lam Tanuki,pong...pong...
My friend, it's pong... pong...
How great. I borrow this one, Doraemon
Well, wait Suneo
Well, turn from here. It's
the store stree,how come...
How come this way...
Set up by Tanuki'?
In this scientific time...
Strange, go home
Well, original road disappears
No more kidding, even no way...
Even lost your way in such big mountain?
Go over there and see
it's soon sun set
Very bad
Which way would be better?
Is anybody for help?
It's wolf, help!
Well, there is a hut.
Wonderful we can spend a night here.
Is there anybody?
Wow beautiful woman
Don't; you fell
lonely living here alone?
What are you talking about, Suneo?
Over slept?
Wow, it seems very tasteful food.
I am very hungry when lost my way in the
mountain. Can I get some food?
I want to start
It does not work.
It seems even more stranger
you must be fox or Tanuki
Let me pull out your tail.
'WHY
Don't"fl:'
Show your real face.
Suneo is crazy...
Help
You dared to cheat me.
Hurry up, wake up, Suneo
Mon... it's monkey
What do you say
Fat Gian
Shizuka, Sorry
Stop, Suneo don't run away.
Help
Stop there, you.
Suneo has learnt a lesson.
Very happy, hahaha...
Stop, Suneo...
Damned guy
What's the matter? How come
Nobita gets a face of Tanuki?
Even mom say this...
Somebody's face is round
Somebody's face is long
Somebodys face is square
Somebody's face is triangle
If cry, become angry
play temper
Crying one will become a devil.
But be happy and laugh.
Everybody's face is actually round.